Guide to the Walter Thabit papers, 1950-2004
Thabit, Walter papers, 1950-2004
- Series IV. Department of Transportation
  - Administrative (DA)
    - DA-15: Sub-Regional Work Program (Box 18, Folder 10)
      Portions of the bureau's work program.
    - DA-16: Monthly Status Report, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      Description of day-to-day work and progress
    - DA-17: Monthly Status Report, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - DA-18: Personnel- DOT T of O's, Misc (Box 18, Folder 13)
      A variety of items relating to personnel, corruption, and plain miscellaneous
    - DA-19: Personnel- Resumes (Box 18, Folder 14)
      Staff under Thabit at one time or another
    - DA-20: Personnel Practices (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - DA-21: Staff and Personnel Memos (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - DA-22: Personnel (Box 18, Folder 17)
      Mostly related to ferry program
    - DA-23: Time Sheets (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - DA-24: Time Sheets, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - DA-25: Time Sheets, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - City Streets (DC)
    - DC-A1: City Streets - Second Draft (Box 18, Folder 21)
      When Thabit was brought onto the project. The draft was filled with error.
    - DC-1: City Streets (Box 18, Folder 22)
      Early Material
    - DC-2: II Bridge Rehabilitation Program (Box 18, Folder 23)
      Complicated program included in report
    - DC-3: City Streets/Upgrading I and III Background (Box 18, Folder 24)
      Material on the other two difficult chapters
    - DC-4: City Streets- Bicycle Background (Box 18, Folder 25)
      Research into this chapter
    - DC-5: Pedestrian Spaces- Backgrounds (Box 18, Folder 26)
      For the chapter on the creation of more pedestrian and park space from unneeded street area.
    - DC-6: Trucking IX (Box 18, Folder 27)
      Work on this chapter
    - DC-7: Taxi Background (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - DC-8: Old Diskettes City Streets Park and Ride Questionnaire (Box 18, Folder 29)
      Want diskettes containing early version of City Streets report and a park and ride questionnaire.
    - DC-9: City Street- Reviews/Comments, August 1981 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - DC-10: Final Draft Corrections (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - DC-11: City Streets Layout (Box 18, Folder 32)
      Includes copy of the final report
    - DC-12: City Streets- Background Illustration (Box 18, Folder 33)
      Materials related to illustrations and charts used in the final report.
    - DC-13: City Streets- Press/Publicity (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - City Streets (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Small Projects (DS)
    - DS-1: Guide-A-Ride/Jamaica Mall (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - DS-2: Battery Maritime Building- Report (Box 18, Folder 36)
      Assembled the relevant materials into a report.
    - DS-3: The New 39th Street Ferry Terminal Building (Box 18, Folder 37)
      The report
    - DS-4: Surface Transit Information Systems. The Guide-A-Ride Report (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - DS-5: Annual Report- DOT 1984 Draft, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      Reviewed Report.
    - DS-6: Astor Place (Box 19, Folder 2)
      Creating an expanded public space at Astor Place
    - DS-7: Barrow Street (Box 19, Folder 3)
      The effort to close the street to create additional pedestrian space
    - DS-8: Brighton Beach Avenue (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - DS-9: Bedford/Caton/Linden (Box 19, Folder 5)
      Effort to create expanded public space.
    - DS-10: Chatham Square (Box 19, Folder 6)
      Attempt to straighten out a complex intersection
    - DS-11: City Island Helistop (Box 19, Folder 7)
      Approving a medical helistop
    - DS-12: Clarkson Street Ramp (Box 19, Folder 8)
      Controversy over a proposed wheelchair ramp
    - DS-13: Farragut Roat (Box 19, Folder 9)
      Pointing out more ways to increase wheelchair ramp suggestions
    - DS-14: Fulton Street Tree Planing (Box 19, Folder 10)
      Tree planing and wheelchair ramp suggestions
    - DS-15: Kiosk Updating- Background (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - DS-16: Manhattan Waterfront Esplanade (Box 19, Folder 12)
      Subject tackled with limited resources
    - DS-17: 36th/38th Streets Esplanade (Box 19, Folder 13)
      Review of a part of the esplanade to be developed.
    - DS-18: Mini-Projects/Letter Responses 1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      About 2 dozen items
    - DS-19: Mini-Projects/Letters 1984 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - DS-20: Mini-Projects/Letters 1985 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - DS-21: Municipal Parking Facilities- Loses: (Box 19, Folder 17)
      Why some municipal parking facilities were losing money
    - DS-22: Riverside Park Study (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - DS-23: Rector Street Pedestrian Bridge (Box 19, Folder 19)
      Complicated intersection signage and transition problems
    - DS-24: Union Square- Greenmarket Parking (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - DS-25: Water and Fulton Streets (Box 19, Folder 21)
      Congestion and proposed signal and other improvements.
    - DS-26: World Trade Center- Busway (Box 19, Folder 22)
      Trying to accommodate both a busway and a greenmarket
    - DS-27: Bicycle Guidemarkers (Box 19, Folder 23)
      A great deal of work went into these bike route signs
    - DS-28: Prospect Park Bicycle Design (Box 19, Folder 24)
      Park of the Bicycle Guidemarkers Project.
    - DS-29: Blue Zone- Wall Street (Box 19, Folder 25)
      Designing signs announcing this program
    - DS-30: East River Bridges- Graphics (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - DS-31: Illustrations of Signs (Box 19, Folder 27)
      Traffic signs in current use
    - DS-32: East/West Signs (Box 19, Folder 28)
      Attempts to differentiate east side from west side destinations through color and shape
    - DS-33: Light Pole Signs- Background (Box 19, Folder 29)
      Efforts to put parking regulation signs on light poles.
    - DS-34: Light Pole Signs- Background (Box 19, Folder 30)
      Idea for graphics for parking regulation signs
    - DS-35: Museum of Modern Art Design (Box 19, Folder 31)
      Directional Sign
    - DS-36: Pamphlet Design/Covers (Box 19, Folder 32)
      Priority Bus Treatments pamphlet and other items
    - DS-37: Traffic Report to Mayor (Box 19, Folder 33)
      Ambitious presentation
    - DS-38: 200 Scale Maps (Box 19, Folder 34)
      Abortive proposal to obtain a set of base maps for planning and analysis purposes
    - Small Projects D.O.T. (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Safe Pedestrian Facilities (DP)
    - DP-1: Safe Pedestrian Facilities Programming (Box 19, Folder 35)
      Study outline and preliminary reports
    - DP-2: Pedestrian Standards (Box 19, Folder 36)
      Reference material and report review
    - DP-3: Pedestrian Newsletters (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - DP-4: Safe Pedestrian Facilities Jan 15th Presentation (Box 19, Folder 38)
      Talk given at conference
    - DP-5: Dyckman/Nagle (Box 19, Folder 39)
      File on one of the 5 intersections
    - DP-6: ParkRow/Broadway (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - DP-7: Neptune/West 5th (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - DP-8: Bruckner/Hunts Point (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - DP-9: Crames Square Bronx (Box 19, Folder 43)
      Park of DP 8
    - DP-10: Bruckner Report (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - DP-11: Park & 33rd- Background (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - DP-12: Park & 33rd (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - DP-13: Safe Pedestrian Facilities- Implementation (Box 20, Folder 3)
      Work on getting proposed improvements acted on
    - DP-14: Broadway/Park Row Implementation (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - DP-15: Capital Improvements Program (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - DP-16: Safe Pedestrian Facilities: Administration, Pre-1983 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - DP-17: Safe Pedestrian Facilities: Administration, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Safe Pedestrian Facilities (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Safe Pedestrian Facilities - Implementation (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - New Streets (DN)
    - DN-1: New Street- Planning (Box 20, Folder 8)
      Planning development of a large open space behind courthouse
    - DN-2: New Street Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 9)
      Agency Coordination
    - DN-3: Spinola Memo- 290 Broadway (Box 20, Folder 10)
      Another city-owned lot
    - DN-4: City Hall Improvement Program (Box 20, Folder 11)
      Extends to City Hall and Broadway/Park Row.
    - DN-5: Chambers St. Memo (Box 20, Folder 12)
      Making Chambers Street one way.
  - Park and Ride (DPR)
    - DPR-1: Park and Ride- Background (Box 20, Folder 13)
      Agency interest in this prospect
    - DPR-2: Auto Ownership- Zip Code (Box 20, Folder 14)
      Basic Data for the analysis
    - DPR-3: County-to-County Travel; Tri-state (Box 20, Folder 15)
      Useful database for a variety of transportation planning tasks. Used in handicapped planning as well as other projects.
    - DPR-4: Park & Ride Questionnaire (Box 20, Folder 16)
      Use to survey hundreds of drivers parking at municipal lots
    - DPR-5: Park & Ride (Box 20, Folder 17)
      Major analyses and preliminary findings
    - DPR-6: Park & Ride May 15 Presentation (Box 20, Folder 18)
      Findings of the survey
    - Park and Ride (Box 69, Folder 19)
- Series V. Organizations
  - Planners for Equal Opportunity
    - President's file
      - PEO-1: PEO I (Box 7, Folder 1)
        Unorganized files. Contain a variety of material. Contains KEY FILE
      - PEO-2: PEO II (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - PEO-3: PEO III (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - PEO-4: PEO IV (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - PEO-5: PEO V (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - PEO-6: Issues and Positions (Box 7, Folder 6)
        Items dealing with positions taken by PEO
      - PEO-7: New York Task Force (Box 7, Folder 7)
        Critique of New York situation undertaken for a PEO conference program
      - PEO-8: New York Task Force (Box 7, Folder 8)
        New York Chapter materials, "good stuff"
      - PEO-9: Ribicoff Hearings (Box 7, Folder 9)
        PEO's position and attempt to testify at the hearings.
      - PEO-10: 4th Annual Conference (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - PEO-11: "Why we Need Planners for Equal Opportunity" (Box 7, Folder 11)
        An early paper written to describe the organization and its concerns. Not published.
      - PEO-12: Planning Education (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - PEO-13: Clarence Funnye Memorial (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - PEO-14: Planning Commission Coalition (Box 7, Folder 14)
        A group of organizations fighting for minority representation on the City Planning Commission
      - PEO-15: Inter-professional Contacts (Box 7, Folder 15)
        Intermittent and generally unsuccessful
    - New Cities Task Force
      - PEO-16: PEO New Cities (Box 7, Folder 16)
        Correspondence and background
      - PEO-17: New Cities Task Force I (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - PEO-18: New Cities Task Force II (Box 7, Folder 18)
        Materials and thinking on New Cities ("NOT INCLUDED IN THIS ASSEMBLAGE)
      - PEO-19: Urban Life (Box 7, Folder 19)
        Publications of American City Corporation
      - PEO-20: New Cities Library #1 (Box 7, Folder 20)
        Reports and other info
      - PEO-21: New Cities Library #2 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - PEO-22: New Cities Report Background (Box 7, Folder 22)
        Drafts, thinking, pertinent reports
    - General
      - PEO-23: 1972-1973, 1972-1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
        A lot on discussions and negotiations with ASPO (American Society of Planning Officials) and other items
      - PEO-24: Correspondence, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - PEO-25: Final Conclave (Box 7, Folder 25)
        Background on what it was and how it got there
      - PEO-26: 1975 Address List, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Transportation Planning Front (Box 71)
      - PEO Reservations (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - PEO Reunion Program (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - PEO Reunion - Lists (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Final June 19th Responses (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - PEO Responses by June 10th - M-Z (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - PEO Responses by June 10th - A-L (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - PEO Reunion - Background (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - PEO Reunion Program - Background (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - PEO Reunion 3.doc - Program Background (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - PEO Reunion Letters.doc (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Planners Network
    - PN-1: Planning Network Newsletters, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - PN-2: Planning Network Newsletters, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - PN-3: Planning Network Newsletters, 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - PN-4: Planning Network Newsletters, 1988- (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Planners' Network, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Planners Network Conference, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - ADPSR, April 22, 2004 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - ADPSR, 1995-2004 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Smaller Organizations
    - Health Pac Files (O-H)
    - Better Transit Bulletin (O-B)
    - Ekistics (O-E)
    - AIP (American Institute of Planners) (O-A)
      - O-A 1: AIP Board of Examiners I (Box 13, Folder 23)
        AIP Board of Examiners of which Thabit was a member of.
      - O-A 2: AIP Board of Examiners II (Box 13, Folder 24)
        Contains critiques of the process (to become a board member) as well as other items.
      - O-A 3: AIP Local: New York Chapter affairs (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - O-A 4: New Jersey State Board of Planners (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - OR-9: Planners Notebook AIP (Box 41, Folder 18)
        An AIP publication (Original guide says it's "obviously misfiled and mis-prefixed)
    - TVASNAC (O-T)
      - O-T 1: Citizens Committee for the Hudson Valley (Box 13, Folder 27)
        Newsletters
      - O-T 2: TVASNAC II (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - O-T 3: TVASNAC III (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous (O-M)
      - O-M 1: National Economic Development Council (Box 13, Folder 30)
        A black development effort, which succeeded in mounting a single conference.
      - O-M 2: Institute for Policy Studies I (Box 13, Folder 31)
        Series of memoranda of interest to the Community Action groups funded by CEO
      - O-M 3: Suburban Action (Box 13, Folder 32)
        Newsletter of Suburban Action. Activist group seeking housing for low and moderate income families and for minorities in the suburbs
      - O-M 4: Other Housing Organizations (Box 13, Folder 33)
        Newsletters and reports
      - O-M 5: Alex Efthim Defense (Box 13, Folder 34)
        An organization devoted to helping Mr. Efthim keep his university job after being threatened with loss of tenure because of his "advocacy" leanings.
    - Organizations (OR)
      - OR-1: N.Y. Mayoralty Campaign 1977, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 10)
        Koch and Sutton
      - OR-2: Sept 14 Rally - Emergency Campaign (Box 41, Folder 11)
        Voter Registration
      - OR-3: Political Campaigns (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - OR-4: N. Tenants Organization N.T.O. (Box 41, Folder 13)
        National Organization
      - OR-5: Emergency Committee for Low Rent Housing (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - OR-6: NYCDV Committee on Housing (Box 41, Folder 15)
        NY Committee for Democratic Voters
      - OR-7: Urban Planning Aid (Box 41, Folder 16)
        Boston Advocacy Group
      - OR-8: New York Council on Housing (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - OR-9a: Urban Development Corp. (Box 41, Folder 19)
        About Logue and Urban Development Corporation
      - OR-10: Samuels - Housing Position (Box 41, Folder 20)
        While Thabit was housing advisor in campaign
      - OR-11: Howard Samuels (Box 41, Folder 21)
      - OR-12: Ryan for Mayor (Box 41, Folder 22)
      - OR-13: Homefront (Box 41, Folder 23)
        A housing action coalition
      - OR-14: MIT Weekend (Box 41, Folder 24)
        Alumni business
      - OR-15: Sumner Rosen Labor Conference (Box 41, Folder 25)
      - OR-16: Conference on Network 1967-1977, 1967-1977 (Box 41, Folder 26)
      - OR-17: Columbia/Planning School (Box 41, Folder 27)
        Aborted negotiations for Thabit to teach there.
      - OR-18: Met Council on Housing I (Box 41, Folder 28)
        An organization Thabit was associated with for a long time. Very active on behalf of tenants rights, rent control, low rent housing, anti slum clearance, etc.
      - OR-19: Met Council II (Box 42, Folder 1)
        Mostly Newsletters
      - OR-20: Met Council III (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - OR-21: Met Council IV (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - OR-22: CHPC, 1961-1962 (Box 42, Folder 4)
        Thabit served on the board of this citizens housing group for many years.
      - OR-23: CHPC, 1962-1963 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - OR-24: CHPC Planning and Housing Newsletter (Box 42, Folder 6)
        Newsletter issues
      - OR-25: CHPC, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - OR-26: CHPC, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - OR-27: Padwee Research - Tax A.V. RED (Box 42, Folder 9)
        Union research on tax assessment giveaways
      - OR-28: Recreation Committee (Box 42, Folder 10)
        Start of the Parks Council
      - OR-29: City Club Comments I (Box 42, Folder 11)
        A businessman's city-wide civic group
      - OR-30: City Club Comments I (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - OR-30a: City Club Landmarks Conference 5/30/80, May 30, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - OR-31: TVASNAC, 1966-1976 (Box 45, Folder 3)
        Town-Village Aircraft Safety & Noise Abatement Committee - 1976-1977 newsletters
      - OR-32: Frank Housing Bill (Box 45, Folder 4)
        Proposal by Community for Creative Non-Violence
      - OR-33: JPC Survey (Box 45, Folder 5)
        Joint Planning Council. Thabit assisted using one of the firm's survey
      - OR-34: 14th St Rezoning (Box 45, Folder 6)
        Union Square Community Council fight against high bulk zoning around the park.
      - Met Council on Housing (Box 70, Folder 26)
      - CHPC (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - West Side Urban Renewal Area - WSURA (W)
    - W-1: WSURA- Background and Early Plan (Box 14 (KEY FILE- ES 11-22 located in 11, front), Folder 1)
      From adoption of the plan through 1963, before any major action was taken.
    - W-2: WSURA- Background (Box 14, Folder 2)
      General materials relating to plan and community participation
    - W-3: West Side "Tipping Point Case" Legal Documents (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Mostly briefs of plaintiffs and Court of Appeals ruling
    - W-4: Tipping Point Writings (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Writing on the "Tipping Point" by officials and academics with some comments by Thabit
    - W-5: Tipping Point- Agenda (Box 14, Folder 5)
      A tipping point paper by Bill Price
    - W-6: West Side URA- Replanning (Box 14, Folder 6)
      Documents and working papers of replanning efforts in 1973 after the plan had been completed.
    - W-7: West Side Renewal- Replanning (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - W-8: Tipping Network Letter (Box 14, Folder 8)
      Letter about the tipping point and some responses
    - W-9: Tipping Point - General (Box 14, Folder 9)
      More writings and other related items
    - W-10: West Side URA- Conference (Box 14, Folder 10)
      Materials prepared for the 1972 neighborhood conference.
    - Tipping Point (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Tipping Point Publications (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Landmarks Preservation Commission (LP)
    - LP-1: 701 Program, 1976-1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      Program that paid for Thabit's salary. Contains reports and some notion of the subject content
    - LP-2: Future of Historic Preservation in NYC, 1976-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
      A major report which was one of Thabit's main preoccupations during the first year.
    - LP-3: 701 General 1976-1977, 1976-1981 (Box 15, Folder 15)
      More reports and memos
    - LP-4: CD III Façade Easements, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 16)
      Material related to the development of a matching grant facade improvement program
    - LP-5: CD III Implementation, 1976-1983 (Box 15, Folder 17)
      Trying to get the program approved and working
    - LP-6: CD III Rehab Materials, 1976-1984 (Box 15, Folder 18)
      Trying to get other agencies interested in undertaking their rehabilitation efforts at least partly in Historic Districts
    - LP-7: CD III, IV, V, 1976-1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      Progress on CD programs and other initiatives
    - LP-8: Garden of Eden, 1976-1986 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      Special Historic Site
    - LP-9: HD Designation Priorities, 1976-1987 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      Various list of designated and to-be-studied buildings and districts
    - LP-10: LPC, Bronx, Manhattan, Staten Island and Brooklyn, 1976-1988 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      Another 701 file, with reports on landmark concerns in housing action areas.
    - LP-11: Grant Proposals, 1976-1989 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      Funding proposals
    - LP-12: Water Quality Management, 1976-1990 (Box 15, Folder 24)
      Information on the program which didn't have much to do with landmarks.
    - LP-13: Sag Harbor, 1976-1991 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      Application to work on Sag Harbor
    - LP-14: Tax Reform Act, 1976-1992 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      The act and its implications
    - LP-15: Museum of Modern Art- Expansion, 1976-1992 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      Materials on the tower construction proposal
    - LP-16: Computer, 1976-1992 (Box 15, Folder 28)
      Material showing the data on CPC computer with which LPC might link up. (Didn't Happen)
    - LP-17: Grand Central Station- Supreme Court Decision, 1976-1992 (Box 15, Folder 29)
      A copy of decision and memos on some of the most important landmark cases in the nation
    - LP-18: Current- Miscellaneous, 1976-1992 (Box 15, Folder 30)
      Variety of material including old guidebooks
    - LP-19: Miscellaneous- LPC- Memos, 1976-1992 (Box 15, Folder 31)
      Spatt memo to Koch transition team.
    - LP-20: Fort Greene- Community Participation, 1976-1992 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      LPC effort to get some community participation and help in monitoring in historic districts
    - LP-21: Technical Materials- Guidelines, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      Various source materials on guidelines
    - LP-22: Boston Guidelines Materials, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - LP-23: Guidelines, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - LP-24: Guidelines- Monitoring, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      Memo on monitoring historic districts and other items.
    - LP-25: Carroll Gardens Guidelines- Reports, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      Major products of the whole effort
    - LP-26: Carroll Gardens Guidelines- Background, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      Preliminaries and site visits
    - LP-27: Guidelines- Maintenance and Alterations, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      More materials related to guidelines
    - LP-28: Carroll Gardens Guidelines- Programming, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      Carroll Gardens as the demo district
    - LP-29: Landmarks- Early Guidelines Materials, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - LP-30: NYC Guidelines Materials, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      Mostly local source materials
    - LP-31: Legal and Economic Mechanisms- Controls, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      Administrative detail for a study that took a great deal of time. Consultant Study
    - LP-32: Legal and Economic Mechanisms- Report, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      A number of review items.
    - LP-33: Legal and Economic Mechanism Study, Final Review- April 1979, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      Some of the reviews of specific chapters
    - LP-34: W. Thabit Corrections Copy I, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      Latest chapter versions
    - LP-35: W. Thabit Corrections Copy II, 7, 8, 9, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      Copies of chapters 7, 8, 9.
    - LP-36: LPC Commission Handbook, 1976-1992 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      Comprehensive assemblage of information on what the LPC is, what it does and how it does it.
    - LPC - CD III, IV, V (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Landmarks - Law (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - HD Guidelines (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Landmarks - General (Box 72, Folder 30)
- Series VI. Studies
  - Study Proposals (SP)
    - SP-1: Manitoba Health (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Correspondence about doing some health planning for this group
    - SP-2: Youth Services Proposal (Box 6, Folder 11)